<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello">Hello World, BRTADrivingExamActivity!</string>
    <string name="app_name">BRTA Admin Page</string>
    <string name="welcome_to">Welcome To</string>
    <string name="registration_number">Registration Number</string>
    <string name="pin_number">Password</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please Wait ...</string>
    <string name="task_progress">Task is in Progress ...</string>
    <string name="instruction">Exam Instruction</string>

    <string name="helpText1">1. Contestant teams will create 5 (five) sets of questions.
        Each set will contain questions with each of the images given below per category and users (examinees)
        will be presented randomly any 10 questions per category. Contestant teams will create database of
        questions and also create 3 other options for each of the questions along with the right answers.
        Right answers are given below each of road signs in the below images</string>

    <string name="helpText2">2. User (examinee) will login with credentials and starts the exam.
        A timer will start and the exact time of starting the exam will be saved in database.
        When the timer reaches 30 minutes, the application will not let the user answer any more questions.</string>

    <string name="helpText3">3. If any user starts exam and quits, he/she will not be given further access
        If time is over user will be taken to Result screen
        The application database will be designed in such a way so that the results of
        the examinees can be accessed from another application</string>

    <string name="helpText4">4. This document describes the detailed functional and nonfunctional requirements
        for the project to be completed during Final Battle of the BASIS Code Warriors’
        Challenge 2012 (Android Track). Before the onsite contest on the specified date by BASIS,
        contestant teams have to complete the specified features according to this document.
        During the onsite contest, contestant teams will be given some problem sets for professional
        and student categories. There will be 3-4 problems and requirements changes to be done during
        the battle session. Teams are expected to solve the problems and incorporate the requirements
        changes in their project. Application will be tested in emulators and source code will be reviewed
        by the Jury members.</string>

    <string name="helpText5">5. Each question will have weight of 2 (two). For any wrong answer user will be penalized with
        negative marking of 1 (one). so the exam will be out of 100</string>

    <string name="timeRemain">Time Left: </string>
    <string name="timeText">30:00</string>
    <string name="chooseQues">Choose your question set</string>
    <string name="text_view">Category</string>
    <string name="question1">What is the sign?</string>
    <string name="completeAns">(0/0)</string>
    <string name="reportResult">Report Result</string>

</resources>
